Guide to the New York State College of Agriculture 4-H club records, 1918-2018.
New York State College of Agriculture 4-H club records
- Series IV. Newsletters and other Publications
  - 4-H Newsletter #54, 1974-06 (Box 133)
  - 4-H Newsletter #48, 1973-12 (Box 133)
  - 4-H Newsletter #53, 1974-05 (Box 133)
  - 4-H Newsletter #52, 1974-04 (Box 133)
  - 4-H Newsletter #51, 1974-03 (Box 133)
  - 4-H Newsletter #50, 1974-02 (Box 133)
  - 4-H Newsletter #49, 1974-01 (Box 133)
  - 4-H Newsletter #47, 1973-11 (Box 133)
  - 4-H Newsletter #46, 1973-10 (Box 133)
  - 4-H Newsletter #45, 1973-09 (Box 133)
  - 4-H Newsletter #44, 1973-08 (Box 133)
  - 4-H Newsletter #43, 1973-07 (Box 133)
  - 4-H Newsletter #42, 1973-06 (Box 133)
  - 4-H Newsletter #40, 1973-05 (Box 133)
  - 4-H Newsletter #40, 1973-04 (Box 133)
  - 4-H Newsletter #39, 1973-03 (Box 133)
  - 4-H Newsletter #38, 1973-02 (Box 133)
  - 4-H Newsletter #37, 1973-01 (Box 133)
  - 4-H Newsletter #36, 1972-12 (Box 133)
  - 4-H Newsletter #35, 1972-10 (Box 133)
  - 4-H Newsletter #34, 1972-09 (Box 133)
  - 4-H Newsletter #33, 1972-08 (Box 133)
  - 4-H Newsletter #32, 1972-07 (Box 133)
  - 4-H Newsletter #31, 1972-06 (Box 133)
  - 4-H Newsletter #30, 1972-05 (Box 133)
  - 4-H Newsletter #29, 1972-04 (Box 133)
  - 4-H Newsletter #28, 1972-03 (Box 133)
  - 4-H Newsletter #27, 1972-02 (Box 133)
  - 4-H Newsletter #26, 1972-01 (Box 133)
  - 4-H Newsletter #25, 1971-12 (Box 133)
  - 4-H Newsletter #24, 1971-10 (Box 133)
  - 4-H Newsletter #23, 1971-09 (Box 133)
  - 4-H Newsletter #22, 1971-08 (Box 133)
  - 4-H Newsletter #21, 1971-07 (Box 133)
  - 4-H Newsletter #20, 1971-06 (Box 133)
  - 4-H Newsletter #19, 1971-05 (Box 133)
  - 4-H Newsletter #18, 1971-04 (Box 133)
  - 4-H Newsletter #17, 1971-03 (Box 133)
  - 4-H Newsletter #16, 1971-02 (Box 133)
  - 4-H Newsletter #15, 1971-01 (Box 133)
  - 4-H Newsletter #14, 1970-12 (Box 133)
  - 4-H Newsletter #13, 1970-10 (Box 133)
  - 4-H Newsletter #12, 1970-09 (Box 133)
  - 4-H Newsletter #11, 1970-08 (Box 133)
  - 4-H Newsletter #10, 1970-07 (Box 133)
  - 4-H Newsletter #65-#98, 1975-07-1978-08 (Box 134)
  - 4-H Newsletter #102-#119, 1979-01-1980-06 (Box 134)
  - 4-H newsletters and enclosures, 1983-01-1983-02 (Box 141, Folder 1)
  - 4-H newsletters and enclosures, 1983-03-1983-07 (Box 141, Folder 2)
  - 4-H newsletters and enclosures, 1983-08-1983-12 (Box 141, Folder 3)
  - 4-H newsletters and enclosures, 1984-01-1984-12 (Box 141, Folder 4)
  - 4-H newsletters and enclosures, 1985-01-1985-03 (Box 141, Folder 5)
  - 4-H newsletters and enclosures, 1985-04-1985-12 (Box 141, Folder 6)
  - 4-H newsletters and enclosures, 1986-01-1986-12 (Box 141, Folder 7)
  - 4-H newsletters and enclosures, 1987-01-1987-05 (Box 141, Folder 8)
  - 4-H newsletters and enclosures, 1987-06-1987-12 (Box 141, Folder 9)
  - 4-H newsletters and enclosures, 1988-01-1988-08 (Box 141, Folder 10)
  - 4-H newsletters and enclosures, 1988-09-1988-12 (Box 141, Folder 11)
  - 4-H newsletters and enclosures, 1989-01-1989-12 (Box 141, Folder 12)
  - 4-H newsletters and enclosures, 1990-01-1990-12 (Box 141, Folder 13)
  - 4-H newsletters and enclosures, 1991-01-1991-12 (Box 141, Folder 14)
  - 4-H newsletters and enclosures, 1992-01-1992-12 (Box 141, Folder 15)
  - New York State 4-H Newsletter, 1992 (Box 129, Folder 9)
  - 4-H Power of Youth Newsletter, 2010-2013 (Box 146, Folder 32)
  - States' 4-H international exchange programs- windows- newsletter and Tomodachi phrasebook, 2016 (Box 146, Folder 33)
  - Chris Clover 4-H designs, Undated (Box 148, Folder 51)
  - Flyers and brochures concerning 4-H camps, Undated (Box 148, Folder 52)
  - 4-H publicity flyers and brochures, 2000-2014 (Box 148, Folder 53)
  - 4-H youth development flyers and updates, 2004-2012 (Box 148, Folder 54)
  - Extension publications (Box 118)
- Series V. Photographs
  - Photos and negatives (Box 125, Folder 33)
  - Photographs (Box 120)
  - Photographs, including some with Franklin D. Roosevelt and Eleanor Roosevelt (Box 121)
  - Photographs selected from folder 104 in box 121, CD-5003
  - Oversized photographs (Folder 1)
  - A. Club Camps
    - Chenango County, 1924 (Box 135, Folder 1)
    - Delaware County, 1929 (Box 135, Folder 2)
    - Jefferson County, 1925 (Box 135, Folder 3)
    - Jefferson County, 1925 (Box 143, Folder 9)
    - Jefferson County, 1927, 1929 (Box 135, Folder 4)
    - Monroe County (Box 135, Folder 5)
    - Nassau County, 1921 (Box 135, Folder 6)
    - Nassau County, 1925 (Box 135, Folder 7)
    - Nassau County, 1925 (Box 135, Folder 8)
    - Ontario County, 1927, 1928 (Box 135, Folder 9)
    - Oneida County, Otsego County, 1922, 1927-1928 (Box 135, Folder 10)
    - Orange County, 1925 (Box 135, Folder 11)
    - Tioga County, Tompkins County, 1923, 1929 (Box 135, Folder 12)
    - Club camps booklets, 1934, 1936 (Box 135, Folder 13)
    - Club camp- calendar- Camp Van Schoonoven, 1935 (Box 135, Folder 14)
    - Camp Vail (Box 135, Folder 15)
    - Camp Vail, 1931 (Box 135, Folder 16)
    - Camp Vail, 1920-1929 (Box 135, Folder 17)
    - Camp Vail, 1926, 1927, 1929 (Box 135, Folder 18)
    - Camp Vail, 1931 (Box 135, Folder 19)
    - Camp Vail, 1931, 1932 (Box 135, Folder 20)
    - Camp Vail, 1931, 1932 (Box 135, Folder 21)
    - National club camp- New York State delegates - undated (Box 135, Folder 22)
    - National club camp- New York State delegates, 1927-1928 (Box 135, Folder 23)
    - National club camp- New York State delegates, 1929 (Box 135, Folder 24)
    - National club camp- New York State delegates, 1930, 1932 (Box 135, Folder 25)
    - National club camp- New York State delegates, 1931 (Box 135, Folder 26)
    - National club camp- New York State delegates, 1931, 1937 (Box 135, Folder 27)
    - National club camp- New York State delegates, 1932 (Box 135, Folder 28)
    - Camp Pyrke, 1932, 1933, 1935 (Box 137, Folder 2)
    - Camp Pyrke, 1936, 1937, 1938 (Box 143, Folder 11)
    - Camp Doush- two copies, 1930 (Box 137, Folder 2)
    - Camp Letchworth, 1939 (Box 139, Folder 73)
    - Camp in Ontario County, 1990-1999 (Box 143, Folder 12)
    - Migrant camp- Owahta,Cortland County, 1990-1999 (Box 143, Folder 12)
  - B. Shows
    - Dairy show, 1923 (Box 135, Folder 29)
    - Dairy show, 1923 (Box 135, Folder 30)
    - Champion cattle, 1927, 1928, 1929 (Box 135, Folder 31)
    - Baby beef show champions, 1929 (Box 135, Folder 32)
    - Baby beef show champions, 1929 (Box 135, Folder 33)
    - Baby beef show, 1930 (Box 135, Folder 34)
    - Winner of National Moses Leadership trophy - Roscoe Owens, 1931 (Box 135, Folder 35)
    - State Fair champions, 1924 (Box 135, Folder 36)
    - Champion dairy, 1929 (Box 135, Folder 37)
    - State Fair demonstrations, 1921, 1923 (Box 135, Folder 38)
    - Stock judging contest- Allegheny County; girls calf project- Chemung County, 1919 (Box 136, Folder 1)
    - G.L.F. scholarship winners- winter short course, 1920 (Box 136, Folder 2)
    - National dairy show, 1923 (Box 136, Folder 3)
    - Dairy show, 1923 (Box 136, Folder 4)
    - Poultry show- Madison Square Garden; poultry judging team- Madison Square Garden, 1928, 1928 (Box 139, Folder 67)
    - Poultry judging teams, 1930-1939 (Box 139, Folder 68)
    - Champion animals- Steuben County, 1990-1993 (Box 146, Folder 34)
    - Champion animals- Steuben County, 1990-1993 (Box 146, Folder 35)
    - Champion animals- Steuben County, 1995-1999 (Box 146, Folder 36)
    - Champion animals- Steuben County, 1995-1999 (Box 146, Folder 37)
    - Champion animals- Steuben County, 1990-1999 (Box 146, Folder 38)
    - Champion animals- Steuben County, 1993 (Box 146, Folder 39)
    - Champion animals- Steuben County, 1994-1996 (Box 146, Folder 40)
  - C. Projects
    - Dairy project- Onondaga County, 1924 (Box 135, Folder 39)
    - Dairy project- Tompkins County, farm shop - Ontario County, Junior Field Days, 1925, 1929 (Box 135, Folder 39b)
    - Project workers (Box 135, Folder 40)
    - Corn project (Box 135, Folder 41)
    - Corn project- Allegheny County, 1918 (Box 143, Folder 2)
    - Corn project- Nassau County, 1919 (Box 135, Folder 42)
    - Corn project- Oswego County, 1922 (Box 135, Folder 43)
    - Corn project- Livingston County, Schoharie County, 1922, 1920 (Box 135, Folder 44)
    - Corn project- various counties, 1918-1929 (Box 143, Folder 3)
    - Calf project- Putnam County, Schoharie County, Livingston County, 1920, 1918, 1920, 1922 (Box 135, Folder 45)
    - Calf project- Oneida County, 1921 (Box 135, Folder 46)
    - Calf project- Otsego County, 1921, 1922 (Box 135, Folder 47)
    - Calf project- Genesee County, Monroe County, 1924, 1922, 1924 (Box 135, Folder 48)
    - Calf project- Onondaga County, Jefferson County, 1924, 1925 (Box 135, Folder 49)
    - Calf project- Schuyler County, Delaware County, 1925 (Box 135, Folder 50)
    - Calf project- Oswego County, Schuyler County, Livingston County, Ontario County, 1925, 1930, 1924 (Box 135, Folder 50b)
    - Calf project (Box 135, Folder 51)
    - Otsego County, Oneida County, 1920, 1921 (Box 135, Folder 52)
    - Calf projects- negatives (Box 135, Folder 53)
    - Calf project- Schoharie County, Steuben County, 1918, 1919 (Box 135, Folder 54)
    - Clothing project- Chemung County, Nassau County, 1922 (Box 135, Folder 55)
    - Clothing project- Nassau County, 1921 (Box 135, Folder 56)
    - Calf project- Erie County, Wyoming County, College of Agriculture, 1921, 1922, 1925 (Box 135, Folder 57)
    - Ontario County, Orange County, St. Lawrence County, 1924, 1924, 1928 (Box 135, Folder 58)
    - Calf project (Box 136, Folder 5)
    - Calf project, 1922 (Box 136, Folder 6)
    - Calf project (Box 136, Folder 7)
    - Calf project- Monroe County; calf feeding demonstration team- Erie County, 1924, 1920 (Box 136, Folder 8)
    - Calf project- Orange County, 1924 (Box 136, Folder 9)
    - Calf project- Erie County; calf club, 1923, 1921 (Box 136, Folder 10)
    - Calf project (Box 136, Folder 11)
    - Calf project- Ontario County, Otsego County, 1924, 1921, 1924 (Box 136, Folder 12)
    - Calf project- Monroe County, 1923, 1930 (Box 136, Folder 13)
    - Calf project- Livingston County, 1921-22 (Box 136, Folder 14)
    - Baby beef project- Genesee County, 1930 (Box 136, Folder 15)
    - Beef project and colt project, 1920-1929 (Box 139, Folder 13)
    - Calf and rabbit projects, 1940-1949 (Box 139, Folder 14)
    - Forestry projects- various projects, 1940-1949 (Box 139, Folder 15)
    - Garden projects- various counties, 1917-1918 (Box 139, Folder 16)
    - Garden projects- various counties, 1917-1929 (Box 139, Folder 17)
    - Garden projects, 1918-1929 (Box 143, Folder 4)
    - Garden projects- various counties, 1920-1929 (Box 139, Folder 18)
    - Garden projects- various counties, 1920-1929 (Box 139, Folder 19)
    - Garden projects- various counties, 1920-1929 (Box 139, Folder 20)
    - Garden projects- various counties, 1920-1929 (Box 139, Folder 21)
    - Garden projects- various counties, 1920-1929 (Box 139, Folder 22)
    - Garden projects- various counties, 1920-1929 (Box 139, Folder 23)
    - Garden projects- various counties, 1920-1929 (Box 139, Folder 24)
    - Garden projects- various counties, 1920-1929 (Box 139, Folder 25)
    - Garden projects- various counties, 1920-1929 (Box 139, Folder 26)
    - Garden projects- various counties, 1920-1929 (Box 139, Folder 27)
    - Pig projects- various counties, 1918 (Box 139, Folder 28)
    - Pig projects- various counties, 1920-1929 (Box 139, Folder 29)
    - Pig projects- various counties, 1920-1929 (Box 139, Folder 30)
    - Pig projects- various counties, 1920-1929 (Box 139, Folder 31)
    - Pig projects- various counties, 1920-1929 (Box 139, Folder 32)
    - Pig projects- various counties, 1920-1929 (Box 139, Folder 33)
    - Pig projects- various counties, 1920-1929 (Box 139, Folder 34)
    - Potato projects- various counties, 1920-1929 (Box 139, Folder 37)
    - Potato projects- various counties, 1920-1929 (Box 139, Folder 38)
    - Potato Projects- Various counties, 1920-1929 (Box 139, Folder 39)
    - Potato projects- various counties, 1920-1929 (Box 139, Folder 40)
    - Potato projects- various counties, 1920-1929 (Box 139, Folder 41)
    - Potato Projects- Various counties, 1920-1929 (Box 139, Folder 42)
    - Potato projects- various counties, 1920-1929 (Box 139, Folder 43)
    - Potato projects- various counties, 1920-1929 (Box 139, Folder 44)
    - Potato projects- various counties, 1920-1929 (Box 139, Folder 45)
    - Potato projects- various counties, 1920-1929 (Box 139, Folder 46)
    - Potato projects- various Counties, 1920-1929 (Box 139, Folder 47)
    - Potato projects- various counties, 1920-1929 (Box 139, Folder 48)
    - Potato projects- various counties, 1920-1929 (Box 139, Folder 49)
    - Potato project- Steuben County, 1923 (Box 143, Folder 2)
    - Poultry projects- various counties, 1920-1929 (Box 139, Folder 50)
    - Poultry projects- various counties, 1920-1929 (Box 139, Folder 51)
    - Poultry projects- various counties, 1920-1929 (Box 139, Folder 52)
    - Poultry projects- various counties, 1920-1929 (Box 139, Folder 53)
    - Poultry projects- various counties, 1920-1929 (Box 139, Folder 54)
    - Poultry projects- various counties, 1920-1929 (Box 139, Folder 55)
    - Poultry projects- various counties, 1920-1929 (Box 139, Folder 56)
    - Poultry projects- various counties, 1920-1929 (Box 139, Folder 57)
    - Poultry projects- various counties, 1920-1929 (Box 139, Folder 58)
    - Poultry projects- various counties, 1920-1929 (Box 139, Folder 59)
    - Poultry projects- various counties, 1920-1929 (Box 139, Folder 60)
    - Poultry projects- various counties, 1920-1929 (Box 139, Folder 61)
    - Poultry projects- various counties, 1920-1929 (Box 139, Folder 62)
    - Poultry projects- various counties, 1920-1929 (Box 139, Folder 63)
    - Poultry projects- various counties, 1920-1929 (Box 139, Folder 64)
    - Poultry projects- various counties, 1920-1929 (Box 139, Folder 65)
    - Poultry projects- various counties, 1920-1929 (Box 139, Folder 66)
    - Sheep projects- various counties, 1920-1929 (Box 139, Folder 70)
    - Sheep projects- various counties, 1920-1929 (Box 139, Folder 71)
    - Sheep projects- various counties, 1920-1929 (Box 139, Folder 72)
  - D. Meetings, National Congress, County Groups
    - National Congress- New York State delegates, 1933 (Box 135, Folder 59)
    - National Congress- New York State delegates, 1934 (Box 135, Folder 60)
    - National Club Camp- New York State delegates, 1935, 1936 (Box 135, Folder 61)
    - National Congress, 1941 (Box 135, Folder 62)
    - National Congress- New York State county groups, 1948 (Box 135, Folder 63)
    - National Congress- New York State county groups, 1948 (Box 135, Folder 64)
    - State Club Congress, 1932 (Box 137, Folder 1)
    - State Club Congress, 1933 (Box 137, Folder 2)
    - State Club Congress, 1947 (Box 137, Folder 2)
    - State Club Congress- county groups, 1948 (Box 135, Folder 65)
    - Rural electrification contest winners, 1942, 1941 (Box 135, Folder 66)
    - Club meetings- Oneida County, Tioga County, 1922, 1923 (Box 135, Folder 67)
    - Club council- Otsego County, Nassau County, 1928 (Box 135, Folder 68)
    - Club meetings- Monroe County, Nassau County, 1930, 1922, 1930 (Box 135, Folder 69)
    - Club- Tompkins County, 1929 (Box 135, Folder 70)
    - Club meeting- Tompkins County, 1923, 1929 (Box 135, Folder 71)
    - Club- recreation- Tompkins County, 1929 (Box 143, Folder 8)
    - Club, 1944 (Box 135, Folder 72)
    - Club- Greene County (Box 135, Folder 73)
    - Club- Photos unidentified (Box 135, Folder 74)
    - Club- Ontario County, 1933 (Box 136, Folder 16)
    - Club - Nassau County; thumb nail photos of clubs from various states, 1944 (Box 136, Folder 17)
    - Club Congress (Box 138, Folder 27)
    - Club Congress (Box 138, Folder 28)
    - Club Congress, 1928 (Box 138, Folder 32)
    - Club Congress, 1960 (Box 138, Folder 33)
    - Club Congress (Box 138, Folder 34)
    - Club Congress (Box 138, Folder 35)
    - Club Congress (Box 138, Folder 36)
    - Club Congress, 1980-1989 (Box 138, Folder 37)
    - Club Congress, 1985 (Box 138, Folder 38)
    - National 4-H Congress, 1940-1949 (Box 138, Folder 59)
    - National 4-H Congress, 1950-1959 (Box 138, Folder 60)
    - National 4-H Congress, 1950-1959 (Box 138, Folder 61)
    - National 4-H Congress, 1960-1979 (Box 138, Folder 62)
    - Cooperative Extension 4-H, 1976 (Box 146, Folder 41)
    - 4-H Congress, 1987 (Box 146, Folder 41)
  - E. Clubs
    - Club activities, 1920-1939 (Box 143, Folder 6)
    - Calf club- Jefferson County, 1924 (Box 135, Folder 76)
    - Senior Boy's Club- Delaware County, county council officers- Rensselaer County (Box 135, Folder 77)
    - Corn club- Oswego County, 1923 (Box 135, Folder 78)
    - Calf club- Delaware County Fair, 1930, 1934 (Box 135, Folder 79)
    - Calf club- Oneida County, 1919 (Box 135, Folder 80)
    - Calf club- Niagara County, Nassau County, 1921, 1919 (Box 135, Folder 81)
    - Chenango County Club Band (Box 135, Folder 82)
    - Food club- Monroe County, Onondaga County, Erie County, 1924, 1924, 1923 (Box 135, Folder 83)
    - Clothing club- Monroe County, Genesee County, Nassau County, 1924, 1924, 1922 (Box 135, Folder 84)
    - Clothing club- Nassau County, 1923 (Box 143, Folder 8)
    - Food preparation- college, clothing club - college, 1925 (Box 135, Folder 85)
    - Clothing club- Monroe County, Schoharie County, Oneida County, 1924, 1923, 1921 (Box 135, Folder 86)
    - Clothing club- Jefferson County, Otsego County, Allegheny County, 1922, 1922, 1919 (Box 135, Folder 87)
    - Clothing club- Erie County, Nassau County, Madison County, 1921, 1923, 1924 (Box 135, Folder 88)
    - Club- Nassau County, Orange County- Farmers' Week, unidentified photos, 1925 (Box 135, Folder 89)
    - Clothing club- Monroe County, Orange County, Putnam County, 1923, 1924, 1919 (Box 135, Folder 90)
    - Clothing club- Monroe County, Nassau County, Otsego County, 1923, 1923, 1922 (Box 135, Folder 91)
    - Clothing club- Onondaga County, Tompkins County, Oneida County, 1924, 1924, 1921 (Box 135, Folder 92)
    - Clothing club - Chenango County, Otsego County, Davenport, New York, 1920, 1922, 1924 (Box 135, Folder 93)
    - Outdoor club meeting- Nassau County, window demonstration- Chemung County, training class- Delaware County, 1921, 1922, 1923 (Box 135, Folder 94)
    - Calf club round-up- St. Lawrence County, 1927, 1929 (Box 136, Folder 18)
    - Calf club- Schoharie County, 1919 (Box 136, Folder 19)
    - Calf club- Saratoga County, 1920 (Box 136, Folder 20)
    - Calf club- Jefferson County, 1922-1923 (Box 136, Folder 21)
    - Calf club- Oneida County, 1920-21 (Box 136, Folder 22)
    - Calf club- Oneida County, 1920 (Box 136, Folder 23)
    - Dramatics festival- State Club Congress, State Club Congress groups, 1932,1936 (Box 140, Folder 54)
    - State Club Council- Allegheny, Broome counties, 1940-1959 (Box 140, Folder 55)
    - State Club Council- Albany, Cattaraugus, Cayuga counties, 1940-1959 (Box 140, Folder 56)
    - State Club Council- Chautauqua County, 1940-1959 (Box 140, Folder 57)
    - State Club Council-Chemung County, 1940-1949 (Box 140, Folder 58)
    - State Club Council- Chenango County, 1940-1959 (Box 140, Folder 59)
    - State Club Council- Clinton, Columbia, Dutchess counties, 1940-1959 (Box 140, Folder 60)
    - State Club Council- Erie, Essex, Franklin counties, 1940-1959 (Box 140, Folder 61)
    - State Club Council- Fulton County, 1940-1959 (Box 140, Folder 62)
    - State Club Council- Jefferson County, 1940-1949 (Box 140, Folder 63)
    - State Club Council- Lewis, Livingston, Madison counties, 1940-1959 (Box 140, Folder 64)
    - State Club Council- Monroe County, 1940-1959 (Box 140, Folder 65)
    - State Club Council- Montgomery County, 1940-1959 (Box 140, Folder 66)
    - State Club Council- Ontario, Orange counties, 1940-1959 (Box 140, Folder 67)
    - State Club Council- Orleans County, 1940-1959 (Box 140, Folder 68)
    - State Club Council- Nassau, Oneida, Onondaga Counties, 1940-1959 (Box 140, Folder 69)
    - State Club Council- Oswego, Otsego counties, 1940-1959 (Box 140, Folder 70)
    - State Club Council- Rensselaer, Rockland counties, 1940-1959 (Box 140, Folder 71)
    - State Club Council- Schoharie County, 1940-1959 (Box 140, Folder 72)
    - State Club Council- St. Lawrence County, 1940-1959 (Box 140, Folder 73)
    - State Club Council- Steuben, Sullivan Counties, 1940-1959 (Box 140, Folder 74)
    - State Club Council- Washington, Wayne Counties, 1940-1959 (Box 140, Folder 75)
    - State Club Council- Ulster, Warren counties, 1940-1959 (Box 140, Folder 76)
    - State Club Council- Indian representation, 1935 (Box 140, Folder 77)
    - State Club Council- group shot, four unidentified county clubs, 1948 (Box 140, Folder 78)
    - Six unidentified county clubs, 1940-1949 (Box 140, Folder 79)
    - Photo Club Day- newspaper article, 1918 (Box 139, Folder 35)
    - Potato clubs- various counties, 1920-1929 (Box 139, Folder 36)
    - Sewing class- Nassau County, 1923 (Box 139, Folder 69)
  - F. Shops
    - Farm shops (Box 135, Folder 95)
    - Farm shops- Otsego County, Ontario County, 1922, 1925 (Box 135, Folder 96)
    - Farm shops- Jefferson County, 1924 (Box 135, Folder 97)
    - Farm shops- Ontario County, 1925 (Box 135, Folder 98)
    - Farm shops- Ontario County, 1925 (Box 137, Folder 1)
    - Farm shops- Delaware County, Wyoming County, State Fair, 1927, 1925, 1924 (Box 135, Folder 99)
    - Crate shop- Chemung County, electric demo, corn demonstration, 1914, 1945, 1920 (Box 135, Folder 100)
    - Woodshop, 1917 (Box 143, Folder 1)
  - G. Fairs and Field Days
    - Calves- state fair, 1920-1929 (Box 135, Folder 101)
    - Calves- county fairs, 1920-1939 (Box 135, Folder 102)
    - County fairs- Delaware, Nassau, Chenango, Otsego, 1923, 1921, 1930, 1922 (Box 135, Folder 103)
    - County fairs- Tioga County, Delaware County, Lewis County, 1923, 1930, 1943 (Box 135, Folder 104)
    - School fairs- Jefferson County, Schoharie County, 1924, 1922 (Box 135, Folder 105)
    - Boys off to school fair- Jefferson County, 1922 (Box 143, Folder 7)
    - Fair parade- Otsego, State Fair, 1922, 1920 (Box 135, Folder 106)
    - County fairs, 1920 (Box 135, Folder 107)
    - State fairs, 1920-1929 (Box 135, Folder 108)
    - Community fairs- Rensselaer County, Schoharie County, Onondaga County, 1924, 1923, 1943 (Box 135, Folder 109)
    - Fairs - Jefferson County, Otsego County, Erie County, 1923, 1922, 1923 (Box 135, Folder 110)
    - Exhibits, 1930-1939 (Box 143, Folder 10)
    - Parade at New York State Fair, 1928 (Box 137, Folder 2)
    - Gathering, 1924 (Box 137, Folder 2)
    - New York State Fair, 1950-1959 (Box 138, Folder 44)
    - New York State Fair, 1960-1969 (Box 138, Folder 45)
    - New York State Fair- 4-H dress revue, 1960-1969 (Box 138, Folder 46)
    - New York State Fair- exhibits, 1960-1969 (Box 138, Folder 47)
    - New York State Fair - exhibits, 1960-1969 (Box 138, Folder 48)
    - New York State Fair, 1967 (Box 138, Folder 49)
    - New York State Fair, 1967 (Box 138, Folder 50)
    - New York State Fair, 1970-1979 (Box 138, Folder 51)
    - New York State Fair, 1987-1988 (Box 138, Folder 52)
    - New York State Fair, 1990-1999 (Box 138, Folder 53)
    - New York State exposition, 1940-1949 (Box 138, Folder 54)
    - New York State exposition, 1965 (Box 138, Folder 55)
    - New York State exposition, 1966 (Box 138, Folder 56)
    - New York State exposition, 1967 (Box 138, Folder 57)
    - Achievement days- various counties, 1923-1931 (Box 139, Folder 74)
    - Delaware County picnic- Governor Roosevelt attended, 1930 (Box 139, Folder 75)
    - Field Days at Cornell- arriving, 1920-1929 (Box 139, Folder 76)
    - Field Day groups- arriving, 1920-1929 (Box 139, Folder 77)